(CELL DOOR BUZZES)
(PANTING)
(MUTTERS):
I need to tell...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIGHS)
- Hey.
Alonzo?
Alonzo, we...
We're gonna have a baby.
TISH: I should have said
already, we're not married.
That means more to him
than it does to me,
but I understand how he feel.
Fonny is 22.
I'm 19.
I'm glad, Fonny.
I'm glad. Don't you worry.
(LAUGHING)
You tell my daddy?
- Not yet.
- You tell your folks?
Not yet, but don't worry
about them.
I just wanted to tell you first.
A baby.
What you gonna do?
I'm gonna do
just like I've been doin'.
I'm gonna work up to
just about the last month
and then Mama and Sis
will take care for me.
You ain't got to worry.
And, anyway, we'll have you
out of here before then.
Are you sure about that?
I'm always sure about that.
I love you.
I love you, too.