Great moments...
...are born from great opportunity.
That's what you have here tonight, boys.
That's what you've earned here tonight.
One game.
If we played them ten times,
they might win nine.
But not this game.
Not tonight.
Tonight we skate with them.
Tonight we stay with them.
And we shut them down because we can.
Tonight we are
the greatest hockey team in the world.
You were born to be hockey players.
Every one of you.
And you were meant to be here tonight.
This is your time.
Their time is done.
It's over.
I'm sick and tired of hearing about what
a great hockey team the Soviets have.
Screw them. This is your time.
Now, go out there and take it.
Hold up here a second.
We're just gonna wait for the OK.
- We're all set.
- All right. Go ahead and send them in.
OK. It's time.
Come on, Jimmy.
Come on, Buzzy. Let's hustle.
Come on, Brotz. Let's go, Strobel.
Rizzo.
USA! USA! USA!