Hey, kids.
How you boys doin'?
Hey, keep chillin'.
You know who we are?
We're associates of your
business partner, Marsellus Wallace.
You do remember
your business partner, don't you?
Now, let me take
a wild guess here.
- You're Brett, right?
- Yeah.
I thought so. You remember
your business partner Marsellus Wallace,
don't ya, Brett?
Yeah, I remember.
Good. Looks like me and Vincent
caught you boys at breakfast.
Sorry about that.
Whatcha havin'?
Hamburgers.
Hamburgers! The cornerstone
of any nutritious breakfast.
What kind of hamburgers?
- Uh, ch-cheeseburgers.
- No, no, no.
Where'd you get 'em?
McDonald's, Wendy's, Jack-in-the-Box?
- Where?
- Uh, Big Kahuna Burger.
Big Kahuna Burger!
That's that Hawaiian burger joint.
I hear they got some tasty burgers.
I ain't never had one myself. How are they?
They're- They're good.
You mind if I try
one of yours?
- This is yours here, right?
- Yeah.
Mmmm.
This is a tasty burger!
Vincent!
You ever had
a Big Kahuna burger?
Want a bite?
They're real tasty.
- I ain't hungry.
- Well, if you like burgers, give 'em a try sometime.
Me, I can't usually get 'em
'cause my girlfriend's a vegetarian,
which pretty much makes me
a vegetarian.
But I do love the taste
of a good burger. Mmmm.
You know what they call
a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese in France?
- No.
- Tell 'em, Vincent.
- A Royale with Cheese.
You know why they call it that?
Uh, because of
the metric system?
Check out the big brain
on Brett!
You're a smart motherfucker.
That's right. The metric system.
- What's in this?
- Sprite.
Sprite. Good.
You mind if I have some of your
tasty beverage to wash this down with?
Go right ahead.
[ Slurping, Sighs ]
That hit the spot.
You. Flock of Seagulls.
You know why we're here?
- Why don't you tell my man Vince here
where you got the shit hid. - It's over-
I don't remember askin' you
a goddamned thing!
You were sayin'?
It's in the cupboard.
N-No, the one
by your kn-knees.
[ Pans Rattling ]
[ Rattling Continues ]
[ Hit Man ]
We happy?
Vincent?
- We happy?
- Yeah, we happy.
[ Sighs ]