How do you distinguish yourself
in a population of people
who all got 1600 on their SATs?
- I didn't know they take SATs in China.
- They don't.
I wasn't talking about China anymore,
I was talking about me.
You got a 1600?
Yes. I could sing in an a Capella group,
but I can't sing.
Does that mean you actually
got nothing wrong?
I could row crew or invent a $25 PC.
Or you could get into a final club.
Or I get into a final club.
You know, from a woman's perspective,
sometimes not singing in
an a Capella group is a good thing.
This is serious.
On the other hand,
I do like guys who row crew.
Well, I can't do that.
I was kidding.
And, yes, I got nothing wrong on the test.
- Have you ever tried?
- I'm trying right now.
- To row crew?
- To get into a final club.
To row crew? No.
Are you, like, whatever, delusional?
Maybe it's just sometimes
you say two things at once.
I'm not sure which one
I'm supposed to be aiming at.
But you've seen guys who row crew, right?
No.
Okay, well, they're bigger than me.
They're world-class athletes.
And a second ago,
you said you like guys who row crew
so I assumed you had met one.
I guess I just meant I like the idea of it.
You know, the way a girl likes cowboys.
Okay.
Should we get something to eat?
Would you like to talk
about something else?
No. It's just since the beginning of
the conversation about finals club,
I think I may have missed a birthday.
There are really more people in China with
genius IQs than the entire population...
The Phoenix is the most diverse.
The Fly Club... Roosevelt punched the Porc.
Which one?
The Porcellian, the Porc.
It's the best of the best.
- Which Roosevelt?
- Theodore.
Is it true that they send a bus around
to pick up girls
who want to party with
the next Fed chairman?
So you can see why
it's so important to get in.
Okay, well, which is the easiest to get into?
- Why would you ask me that?
- I was just asking.
None of them. That's the point.
My friend Eduardo made $300,000
betting oil futures one summer
and Eduardo won't come close to getting in.
The ability to make money doesn't
impress anybody around here.
Must be nice.
He made $300,000 in a summer?
- He likes meteorology.
- You said it was oil futures.
You can read the weather,
you can predict the price of heating oil.
I think you asked me that
because you think
the final club that's easiest to get into
is the one where I'll have the best chance.
I... What?
You asked me which one was
the easiest to get into
because you think that that's the one
where I'll have the best chance.
The one that's the easiest to get into
would be the one
where anybody has the best chance.
You didn't ask me which one
was the best one,
you asked me which one
was the easiest one.
I was honestly just asking, okay?
I was just asking to ask.
- Mark, I'm not speaking in code.
- Erica.
You're obsessed with finals clubs.
You have finals clubs OCD
and you need to see someone about it
who will prescribe you
some sort of medication.
You don't care if the side effects
may include blindness.
Final clubs. Not "finals clubs."
And there's a difference between
being obsessed and being motivated.
Yes. There is.
Well, you do.
That was cryptic, so you do speak in code.
I didn't mean to be cryptic.
I'm just saying I need to do
something substantial
in order to get the attention of the clubs.
- Why?
- Because they're exclusive.
And fun, and they lead to a better life.
Teddy Roosevelt didn't get elected president
because he was a member
of the Phoenix Club.
He was a member of the Porcellian,
and yes, he did.
Well, why don't you just concentrate
on being the best you you can be?
Did you really just say that?
I was kidding.
Just because something's trite
doesn't make it less true.
I wanna try to be straightforward with you
and tell you I think you might
want to be a little more supportive.
If I get in, I will be taking you
to the events and the gatherings,
and you'll be meeting a lot of people
you wouldn't normally get to meet.
You would do that for me?
We're dating.
Okay.
Well, I wanna try and be
straightforward with you
and let you know that we're not anymore.
- What do you mean?
- We're not dating anymore. I'm sorry.
- Is this a joke?
- No, it's not.
You're breaking up with me?
You're gonna introduce me to people
I wouldn't normally
have the chance to meet?
What the... What is that supposed to mean?
- Wait, settle down.
- What is it supposed to mean?
Erica, the reason we're able to sit here
and drink right now
is 'cause you used to sleep
with the door guy.
"The door guy"? His name is Bobby.
I have not slept with the door guy.
The door guy is a friend of mine,
and he's a perfectly good class of people.
And what part of Long Island
are you from, Wimbledon?
- Wait. Wait, wait.
- I'm going back to my dorm.
- Is this real?
- Yes.
- Then wait, I apologize, okay?
- I have to go study.
- Erica?
- Yes?
- I'm sorry, I mean it.
- I appreciate that, but I have to go study.
Come on, you don't have to study.
Let's just talk.
- I can't.
- Why?
Because it is exhausting.
Dating you is like dating a StairMaster.
All I meant is that you're not likely to...
Currently...
I wasn't making a comment
on your appearance.
I was saying that you go to BU.
I was stating a fact, that's all,
and if it seemed rude, then I apologize.
- I have to go study.
- You don't have to study.
Why do you keep saying
I don't have to study?
'Cause you go to BU.
Do you want to get some food?
I am sorry you are not sufficiently
impressed with my education.
And I'm sorry I don't have a rowboat,
so we're even.
- I think we should just be friends.
- I don't want friends.
I was just being polite.
I have no intention
of being friends with you.
I'm under some pressure right now
from my OS class
and if we could just order some food,
I think we should...
Okay, you are probably going to be
a very successful computer person.
But you're gonna go through life
thinking that girls don't like you
because you're a nerd.
And I want you to know from the bottom
of my heart that that won't be true.
It'll be because you're an asshole.