Watch your step.
Come in.
-Very nice house.
-Oh, thank you.
It's very rustic.
-Can I take your jacket?
-No, thank you, I'm fine.
Okay. This way, please.
-Have a seat.
-Thank you.
-How about some tea?
-Oh, no, I'm all right.
-You sure?
-Yes.
I wanted to ask you about a film
that the Avenue may have played
while you were the organist there.
The Most Dangerous Game?
Oh, it's a classic. RKO. 1932.
Fay Wray, Joel McCrea, Leslie Banks.
We've run that picture many times.
In '68, '69?
I'd have to check my records. Why?
Do you remember the Zodiac?
This is about Rick Marshall, isn't it?
-He was a projectionist there, right?
-For a time, yes.
But I have no occasion
to correspond with him these days.
Okay. Well, there is a connection
between one of the Zodiac attacks
and that film.
You mean the symbol?
Hold on.
The Zodiac symbol on film.
It's on the countdown.
It's trimmed off each reel
before it's shown,
but it always arrives with it.
Right there.
The first time I saw it in the papers,
I thought about that.
We got a tip
that Rick left a film canister here
that he told you never to open.
A tip about a mysterious film canister?
Is it true?
Yes.
-Did you open it?
-No.
-May I see it?
-Rick took it back in 1972.
This tip is how you got it in your head
that Rick is the Zodiac?
That and the poster.
The poster?
The poster that Rick drew.
The handwriting is the closest
that we have ever come to a match.
-Rick didn't draw any posters.
-No, he drew this one.
Mr. Graysmith, I do the posters myself.
That's my handwriting.
I won't take any more of your time.
Why don't I just go and find out
when we played that film?
Oh, that's all right.
It's not a problem.
They're just down in the basement.
Not many people
have basements in California.
I do.
You coming, Mr. Graysmith?
The original studio one-sheets,
I always kept for myself.
The cheapo knock-offs
like you brought today
I end up tossing into the back alley.
'69.
You live alone?
Most Dangerous Game ran in May '69.
So, that would be about
nine weeks before
the first Zodiac letter, correct?
Yeah.
Do you think he saw the film
in our theater and was inspired?
Are you sure
there's nobody else in the house?
Would you like
to go upstairs and check?
No.
Thank you. Thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
It's locked.
Thank you.
Good night, Mr. Graysmith!