Ladies and gentlemen,
we are down to the final
two championship words.
One or both of our spellers will walk away
with the first-place trophy.
Dylan, you're up.
"Logorrhea."
May I have the definition, please?
Logorrhea is excessive and often
incoherent talkativeness.
"Logorrhea."
L-
O-G-
O-R-R-
H-E-A.
"Logorrhea"?
Congratulations, Dylan.
You've won the Scripps
National Spelling Bee.
Yes! Yes!
Go get 'em.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please be seated for Akeelah's turn.
♫
"Pulchritude."
It's derived from
the Latin word pulcher,
meaning "beautiful",
- isn't it?
- That's correct.
- P-
- U-
- L-
- C-
- H-
- R-
- I-
- T-
- U-
- D-
E.
"Pulchritude."
Congratulations, Akeelah.
That's what I'm talking about!
You know that feeling
where everything feels right,
where you don't have to worry
about tomorrow or yesterday,
but you feel safe
and know you're doing
the best you can?
There's a word for that feeling.
It's called love.
L-O-V-E.
And it's what I feel for all my family
and all my coaches
in my neighborhood
where I come from,
where I learned how to spell.