(THREE-PIECE COMBO
PLAYS SOFT JAZZ)
Daddy!
(CHUCKLING)
My son, the birdman.
Some uniform, Frank.
What do you think?
Nice.
Sit down.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, Dad... Daddy, have you
gotten the postcards?
Of course.
This fork is ice cold.
No, no, Dad, th-that's
a chilled salad fork.
(WHISPERING)
It's a fancy restaurant, you know.
(SIGHING)
Well, here...
I-I got you something.
What's that?
Open it.
You know what those are, right?
Those are the keys
to a 1965 Cadillac
DeVille convertible.
Brand-new, Dad.
Red with white interior
split seats,
air conditioning, the works.
Are you giving me a Cadillac?
Yeah. I'm giving you
a Cadillac.
Dad, sh-she's parked
downstairs.
When we're done eating lunch
why don't you, you know,
drive on over to Mom's house
pick her up,
take a little joyride?
Do you know what would happen
if the IRS found out
I was driving around
in a new coupe?
I took the train here, Frank.
I'm taking the train home.
All right.
I have plenty of money.
You know, if you
ever, ever need anything...
You worried?
About me?
No, I'm not...
I'm not worried.
You think I can't
buy my own car?
Two mice fell in a
bucket of cream, Frank.
Which one am I?
You're that second mouse.
I went by the store today.
I had to close the
store for awhile.
It's all about timing, Frank.
The goddamn government
knows that.
They hit you when you're down.
I wasn't going to let them
take it from me, so I just...
shut the doors myself,
called their bluff.
Sooner or later,
they'll forget about me.
I understand, I...
Have you told Ma?
She's so stubborn, your mother.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to let her go
without a fight.
I been fighting for us...
(GASPS QUIETLY)
Dad?
Since the day we... we met.
Daddy, out of all those men
you were the one that
took her home, remember that.
200 men, sitting in
that tiny social hall
watching her dance.
What was the name of that town?
Montrichard, Dad.
Yeah.
I didn't speak a word of French
and six weeks later,
she was my wi...
She's your wife.
My son bought me
a Cadillac today.
I think that calls for a toast.
(SOFT JAZZ PLAYING)
(INHALING DEEPLY)
To the best damn pilot
in the sky.
It's not what you think.
I'm just a copilot.
You see these people
staring at you?
These are the most
powerful people
in New York City
and they keep peeking
over their shoulders
wondering where
you're going tonight.
Where you going, Frank?
Dad, nobody's staring at me.
Some place exotic?
Just tell me where you're going.
Los An... Hollywood.
Hollywood.
(SNIFFLES)
(WHISPERING)
The rest of us...
really are suckers.