You know what sucks?
Realizing that everything you believe in
is complete and utter bullshit.
- It sucks.
- What do you mean?
Uh, you know, destiny,
and soul mates, and true love,
and all that childhood
fairy tale nonsense.
You were right.
I-I should have listened to you.
No.
Yeah. What?
What are you smiling at?
- Tom.
- What?
What are you looking at me
like that for?
Well, you know,
I guess it's 'cause...
I was sitting in a deli
and reading Dorian Gray
and... a guy comes up to me...
and asked me about it,
and... now he's my husband.
Yeah. And... so?
So, what if I'd gone to the movies?
What if I had gone
somewhere else for lunch?
What if I'd gotten there
10 minutes later?
It was-
It was meant to be.
And I just kept thinking,
- Tom was right.
- No.
Yeah, I did.
[Laughs]
I did.
It just wasn't me
that you were right about.
I should go.
But I'm really happy to see
that you're doing well.