We ain't talking about baseball!
We talking about you going off
and laying up with another woman,
then bringing it home to me.
That's what we're talking about.
We're not talkin' about no baseball!
Rose, you're not listening to me.
I'm trying to explain it to you
the best way I know how.
It's not easy for me to admit
that I've been standing
in the same place for 18 years!
Well, I've been standing with you!
I've been right here with you, Troy!
I got a life, too.
I gave 18 years of my life
to stand in the same spot as you!
Don't you think
I ever wanted other things?
I had dreams and hopes?
What about my life? What about me?
Don't you think it ever crossed my mind
to want to know other men?
That I wanted to lay up somewhere
and forget about my responsibilities?
That I wanted someone
to make me laugh,
so I could feel good?
You're not the only one
who's got wants and needs.
But I held on to you, Troy.
I took all my feelings,
my wants and needs and dreams,
and I buried them inside you.
I planted a seed
and watched and prayed over it.
I planted myself inside you
and waited to bloom!
And it didn't take me no 18 years
to realize the soil was hard and rocky,
and it wasn't never gonna bloom!
But I held on to you, Troy.
I held you tighter.
You was my husband.
I owed you everything I had.
Every part of me I could find to give you.
And upstairs in that bedroom,
with the darkness falling in on me,
I gave everything I had
to try and erase the doubt
that you wasn't the finest man
in the world.
And wherever you was going,
I was gonna be there with you,
because you was my husband.
'Cause that's the only way
I was gonna survive as your wife.
You always talking about what you give
and what you don't have to give.
But you take, too, Troy.
You take
and don't even know nobody's giving.
You say I take and don't give.
Troy, you're hurting me.
- Troy, you're hurting my arm, let go!
- I gave you everything I got.
Don't you tell that lie on me.
- Mama!
- Don't you tell that lie!
Troy, you're hurting me!
Troy! Troy!
All right. That's strike two.
You stay away from around me, boy.
Don't you strike out.
You're living with a full count.