You died on a Saturday morning.
And I had you placed
here under our tree.
And I had that house of your father's
bulldozed to the ground.
Mama
always said that dying was a part of life.
I sure wish it wasn't.
Little Forrest is doing just fine.
But...
About to start school again soon,
and I make his breakfast, lunch
and dinner every day.
I make sure he combs his hair
and brushes his teeth every day.
Teaching him how to play Ping-Pong.
Okay.
He's really good.
Forrest, you go.
We fish a lot.
(SOBBING) And every night, we read
a book. He's so smart, Jenny.
You'd be so proud of him.
I am.
He wrote you a letter.
And he says I can't read it.
I'm not supposed to,
so I'll just leave it here for you.
Jenny,
I don't know if Mama was right,
or if it's Lieutenant Dan.
I don't know
if we each have a destiny,
or if we're all just floating around
accidental-like on a breeze.
But I think
maybe it's both.
Maybe both is happening
at the same time.
But I miss you, Jenny.
If there's anything you need,
I won't be far away.