Hey, you know you'd be better off shoving that cigarette
up your ass. It'd probably be healthier for you.
- Yeah, I know. It really gets in the way of my yoga.
- You work out, huh?
- What, you lift?
- Yeah.
- Uh, Nautilus?
- No, free weights.
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
- Free weights, huh?
- Yeah, big time. -
Yeah? - Just like that.
- What do you bench?
- 285. What do you bench?
You paint that?
Yeah. You paint? Do you sculpt?
- No.
- Do you like art?
Do you like music?
This is a real piece of shit.
Oh. Well, tell me
what you really think.
Uh, just, uh, the linear
and impressionistic mix...
makes a very muddled composition.
It's also a Winslow Homer rip-off, except
you got whitey, uh, rowin' the boat there.
Well, it's art, Monet.
It wasn't very good.
- That's not really what concerns me though.
- What concerns you?
- Just the colouring.
- You know what the real bitch of it is?
It's paint-by-number.
Is it colour-by-number? Because
the colours are fascinating to me.
- Aren't they, really? What about that?
- You bet.
I think you're about one step away
from cuttin' your fuckin' ear off.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Think I should move to the south
of France, change my name to Vincent?
You ever heard the sayin',
"any port in a storm"?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Maybe that means you.
In what way?
- Uh, maybe you're in the middle of a storm, a big fuckin' storm.
- Yeah, maybe.
The sky's fallin' on your head. The
waves are crashin' over your little boat.
The oars are about to snap.
You just piss in you pants.
You're cryin' for the harbour.
So maybe you do
what you gotta do to get out.
You know, maybe you became
a psychologist.
Bingo. That's it. Let me do my job now.
You start with me. Come on.
- Maybe you married the wrong woman.
- Maybe you should watch your mouth!
Watch it right there, chief,
all right?
Ah.
Mmm, that's it, isn't it?
You married the wrong woman.
What happened?
What, did she leave you?
Was she, you know,
banging some other guy?
If you ever disrespect my wife again,
I will end you.
I will fuckin' end you.
Got that, chief?
- Time's up.
- Yeah.