MARJORIE:
Does it hurt yet? I hope it does.
I hope it hurts like hell.
John Coffey, you've been condemned to
die in the chair by a jury of your peers.
Sentence imposed by a judge
in good standing in this state.
Do you have anything to say
before sentence is carried out?
I'm sorry for what I am.
Please, boss...
...don't put that thing over my face.
Don't put me in the dark.
I's afraid of the dark.
All right, John.
[SOFTLY]
Heaven, I'm in heaven
Heaven, heaven
I'm in heaven
John Coffey...
...electricity shall pass through
your body until you are dead...
...in accordance with state law.
May God have mercy on your soul.
Paul.
You have to say it.
You have to give the order.
COFFEY'S VOICE:
He killed them with they love.
That's how it is every day
all over the world.
Roll on two.
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]