- Mr. Wood.
- Good luck, Your Majesty.
Mr. Wood.
- You've redecorated, Logue.
- I made it cozy.
- Some fresh air.
- There you are, darling.
I'm a thistle-sifter.
I've a sieve of sifted thistles
and a sieve of unsifted thistles.
A sieve of sifted thistles
- Because I'm...
- Bertie. Darling.
Make sure it's not switched on.
Remember, the red light
will blink four times,
then I've asked them to turn it off.
'Cause we don't want that evil eye
staring at you all the way through.
One minute, sir.
I'm sure you'll be splendid.
Forty seconds, sir.
Logue.
However this turns out...
...I don't know how to thank you...
for what you've done.
Knighthood?
Twenty seconds.
Forget everything else,
and just say it to me.
Say it to me as a friend.
In this grave...
..hour..
...perhaps the most fateful
in our history...
...I send...
...to every household of my...
...a-peoples...
...both at home...
...and overseas...
...this message...
...spoken with the same
depth of feeling...
...for each one of you...
...as if I were able
to cross your threshold
and speak to you... myself.
For the second time
in the lives of most of us...
...we are... at...
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
...at war.
Very good.
Over and over again...
...we have tried to find...
...a peaceful way out
of the differences...
...between ourselves...
...and those...
...who are now our... enemies.
But it has been... in vain.
We have been forced into a conflict,
for we are called
to meet the challenge of a principle,
which, if it were to prevail,
would be fatal to any civilized order
in the world.
Such a principle,
stripped of all disguise,
is surely the mere...
...primitive doctrine that might...
...is right.
For the sake of all
that we ourselves hold dean
it is unthinkable
that we should refuse to meet...
...the challenge.
It is to this high purpose
that I now call
my people at home,
and my peoples across the seas,
who will make our cause their own.
I ask them to stand calm
and firm and united
in this time of trial.
The task will be hard.
There may be dark days ahead,
and war can no longer be confined
to the battlefield.
But we can only do the right
as we see the right,
and reverently commit
our cause to God.
If one and all we keep
resolutely faithful to it,
then, with God's help,
we shall... prevail.