[sighs]
Excuse me. What day is it?
Sunday.
Thank you.
[bell tolling]
- [bell tolling continues]
- [choir singing]
[choir singing continues]
[phone ringing]
[Larry] Hi. You've reached
the McPherson family.
Please leave a message.
Thank you.
[beeps]
Hi, Mom and Dad.
It's me. Christine.
It's the name you gave me.
It's a good one.
Dad, this is more for Mom.
Hey, Mom.
Did you feel emotional the first
time that you drove in Sacramento?
I did, and I wanted to tell you,
but we weren't really talking
when it happened.
All those bends I've
known my whole life,
and stores and the whole thing.
[Marion's indistinct voice]
[Marion's indistinct voice
continues]
But I wanted to tell you...
I love you. [sighs]
Thank you. I'm...
Thank you.
...
[inhales]