- Excuse you. You're in my way.
- She's a student. She can't defend you.
Massachusetts Supreme
Judicial Court Ruling 3.03.
See?
- Thank you, David.
- Counselors, approach the bench.
- You're not going up there.
- Oh, yes, I am.
I'm sorry. Maybe you
didn't hear me. You're fired.
Counselors, now! All of you.
Elle Woods, Your Honor.
Rule 3.03 of Supreme Judicial Court
states that a law student
may appear on behalf
of a defendant in criminal proceedings
Your Honor,
I have no problem with this.
- I do. I'm not allowing it.
- But you agreed last night.
In your office,
when we were discussing my career?
The ruling also states that you need
a licensed attorney to supervise you.
- Mr. Callahan?
- That I won't agree to.
I'll supervise, Your Honor.
Well, then, Ms. Woods, proceed.
Thank you, Your Honor.
(chuckling)
- Hi.
Enjoy prison.
Mrs. Windham,
you do realize what you're doing?
Absolutely.
- Oh, my God. There she is. Elle!
- Elle, we came to see your trial.
Oh, look, how cute! There's, like,
a judge and everything. And jury people.
- Vote for Elle!
- Ladies, take a seat.
Go, girl.
Do you swear to tell the whole truth and
nothing but the truth, so help you God?
- I do.
- Be seated.
Ms. Woods, you may
begin your questioning.
First of all, I would like
to point out that,
not only is there
no proof in this case,
but there's a complete
lack of mens rea,
which, by definition,
tells us that there can be no crime
without a... vicious will.
I am aware of the meaning of mens rea.
What I'm unaware of is why
you're giving me a vocabulary lesson
when you should be
questioning your witness.
Yes, Your Honor.
Ms. Windham...
When you arrived back at the house...
...was your father there?
Not that I saw. But like I said,
I went straight upstairs
to take a shower.
And... when you came downstairs,
what happened?
I saw Brooke standing over his body...
...drenched in his blood.
- But Mrs. Windham didn't have a gun?
- No, she'd stashed it by then.
Move to strike that
from the record, Your Honor.
- It's speculation.
- So stricken.
Go ahead.
Ms. Windham, did you hear a shot fired?
No. I was in the shower.
OK.
So... sometime in the 20 minutes
that you were in the shower...
...your father was shot?
I guess.
Your father was shot
while you were in the shower...
...but you didn't
hear the shot because...
...because you were in the shower?
Yes. I was washing my hair.
- (barks)
- Where is she going with this?
- Have a little faith, Gerard.
Ms. Windham,
what had you done earlier that day?
I got up, got a latte,
went to the gym,
got a perm and came home.
Where you got in the shower?
I believe the witness has made it
clear that she was "in the shower."
(all chuckling)
Yes, Your Honor.
Ms. Windham,
had you ever gotten a perm before?
- Yes.
- How many, would you say?
Two a year since I was 12.
You do the math.
You know, a girl in my sorority,
Tracy Marcinko, got a perm once.
We all tried to talk her out of it.
Curls weren't a good look for her.
She didn't have your bone structure.
Aww.
But thankfully, that same day,
she entered the Beta Delta Pi
wet T-shirt contest,
where she was completely
hosed down from head to toe.
Objection! Why is this relevant?
- I have a point. I promise.
- Then make it.
Yes, ma'am.
Chutney, why were Tracy Marcinko's
curls ruined when she got hosed down?
- Because they got wet.
- Exactly.
Because isn't it the first cardinal
rule of perm maintenance
that you're forbidden
to wet your hair for at least 24 hours
after getting a perm
at the risk of deactivating
-the ammonium thioglycolate?
- Yes...
And wouldn't somebody who's had,
say 30 perms before in their life
be well aware of this rule?
And if you weren't washing your hair,
as I suspect you weren't,
because your curls are still intact,
wouldn't you have heard the gunshot?
And if, in fact, you had heard the
gunshot, Brooke Windham
wouldn't have had time to hide
the gun before you got downstairs,
which would mean that you would've
had to have found Mrs. Windham
with a gun in her hand to make
your story plausible. Isn't that right?
She's my age, did she tell you that?
How would you feel if your father
married someone your age?
You, however, had time to hide the gun,
didn't you, Chutney?
- After you shot your father.
- I didn't mean to shoot him!
I thought it was you
walking through the door!
(crowd exclaiming)
Order! Order! Order.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Bailiff, take the witness into custody,
where she will be charged
for the murder of Heyworth Windham.
In the matter of
The State v. Brooke Windham,
this case is dismissed.
Mrs. Windham, you are free to go.
Yes!
(all cheering)