Why did you want to kill yourself?
No, don't answer the question, Frank.
- Richard! Richard!
- He's not gonna answer the question. Frank.
- I wanted to kill myself-
- Don't listen to him.
- I was very unhappy.
- He's sick in his head.
- Richard!
- I'm sorry! I don't think it's an appropriate conversation...
- for a seven-year-old.
- She's gonna find out anyway.
- Okay.
- Go on, Frank.
Why were you unhappy?
Um, well, there are a lot of reasons.
Mainly, though, I fell in love
with someone who didn't love me back.
Who?
One of my grad students.
I was very much in love with him.
Him?
It was a boy?
You fell in love with a boy?
- Yes, I did. Very much so.
- That's silly.
You're right. It was silly.
It was very, very silly.
- There's another word for it.
- Dad.
- So, that's when you tried to kill yourself?
- Well, no.
The boy that I was in love with fell in love
with another man- Larry Sugarman.
- Who's Larry Sugarman?
- Larry Sugarman is, perhaps...
the second most highly regarded
Proust scholar in the U.S.
- Who's number one?
- That would be me, Rich.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
So that's when.
No. What happened was
I was a bit upset...
so I said some things
that I shouldn't have said...
and I did some things
that I shouldn't have done...
and subsequently
I was fired from my job...
and forced to move out of my apartment
and move into a motel.
- And that's when you tried to-
- Well, no.
Actually, all of that was okay.
What happened was two days ago the
MacArthur Foundation, in its infinite wisdom...
awarded a genius grant
to Larry Sugarman.
And that's when I-
Decided to check out early.
Yes. Yes. And I failed
at that as well.
Olive, the important thing
to understand here...
is that Uncle Frank
gave up on himself.
He made a series of foolish choices-
I'm sorry- and he gave up on himself...
which is something winners never do.