You're being so much like your father.
Do not compare me to my father!
I didn't compare you to him.
I said you were acting like him.
You're exactly like your mother.
Everything you were complaining about her,
you're doing. You're suffocating Henry.
First of all, I love my mother.
She was a wonderful mother.
- I'm just repeating what you told me.
- Secondly, how dare you
compare my mothering to my mother!
I may be like my father,
but I am not like my mother!
You are!
And you're like my father!
You're also like my mother!
You're all the bad things
about all of these people!
But mostly your mother.
When we would lie in bed together,
sometimes I would look at you and see her
and just feel so gross!
- I felt repulsed when you touched me!
- You're a slob.
I made all the beds,
closed all cabinets...
The thought of having sex with you
makes me want to peel my skin off.
You'll never be happy, in LA or anywhere.
You'll think you found
some better opposite guy than me,
and in a few years,
you'll rebel against him
because you need to have your voice,
but you don't want a voice.
You just want to fucking complain
about not having a voice!
I think about being married to you,
and that woman is a stranger to me.
- I mean, we had a child's marriage.
- You've regressed.
You've gone back to your life
before you met me, it's pathetic.
People used to tell me that you were
too selfish to be a great artist.
And I used to defend you.
They were absolutely right.
All your best acting is behind you.
You're back to being a hack!
You gaslighted me!
You're a fucking villain!
You want to present yourself as a victim
because it's a good legal strategy?
Fine, but you and I both know
you chose this life!
You wanted it until you didn't!
You used me so you could get out of LA.
I didn't use you.
You did, and then you blamed me for it!
You always made me aware
of what I was doing wrong,
how I was falling short!
Life with you was joyless!
What, so then you had to go
and fuck someone else?
You shouldn't be upset that I fucked her!
You should be upset
that I had a laugh with her!
Do you love her?
No.
But she didn't hate me. You hated me.
You hated me.
You fucked somebody we worked with.
You stopped having sex with me
in the last year.
I never cheated on you.
That was cheating on me!
But there was so much I could have done.
I was a director in my twenties
who came from nothing
and was suddenly on the cover
of fucking Time Out New York!
I was hot shit and I wanted
to fuck everybody and I didn't.
And I loved you
and I didn't want to lose you.
But I'm in my twenties,
and I didn't want to lose that too,
and I kinda did!
And you wanted so much so fast.
I didn't even want to get married.
And fuck it!
There's so much I didn't do.
- Thanks for that!
- You're welcome!
I can't believe
I have to know you forever!
You're fucking insane!
And you're fucking winning!
Are you kidding me?
I wanted to be married.
I'd already lost!
You didn't love me as much as I loved you!
What does that have to do with LA?
What?
You're so merged
with your own selfishness,
you don't even identify it
as selfishness anymore!
You're such a dick!
Every day I wake up
and I hope you're dead!
Dead, like if I could guarantee
Henry would be okay,
I'd hope you'd get an illness,
and then get hit by a car and die!
Oh, God!
I'm sorry.
Me too.