Come on, man.
Give me your head.
Here, let your head
rest in my hand. Relax.
I got you, I promise.
I'm not gon' let you go.
Hey, man, I got you.
There you go.
Ten seconds.
Feel that right there?
You're in the middle
of the world, man.
That's good.
Do like this.
Look at you.
More athletic.
There you go...
there you go.
Yeah.
I think you ready.
I think we got a swimmer.
You wanna try?
You ready to swim?
Go.
Yeah, man!
Yeah!
Let me tell you something, man.
There are black people
everywhere.
Remember that, okay?
No place you can go in the world
ain't got no black people.
We's the first on this planet.
I been here a long time.
But I'm from Cuba.
Lot a black folks in Cuba,
you wouldn't know that
from being here, though.
I was a wild li'l shorty, man,
just like you.
Runnin' around with no shoes on
when the moon was out.
This one time...
I run by this old...
this old lady.
I was runnin', hollerin'...
cuttin' a fool, boy.
This old lady, she stopped me.
She said...
"Running around,
catching up all that light.
In moonlight...
black boys look blue.
You blue.
That's what I gon' call you.
Blue."
So your name Blue?
Nah.
At some point you gotta decide
for yourself who you gon' be.
Can't let nobody make
that decision for you.