Thanks.
Oh, gosh. It's him.
Hey, Hal!
Welcome home, kiddo.
- Get into these arms, you little punk.
- Dad.
Finally.
Oh, I hope you had a lousy time at that
camp because you are not going back.
I missed you too much.
What happened to you, Hal?
Something's changed.
Are you getting taller?
So, what's up, Dad?
I mean, how's Chessy and everybody?
Great. Everybody's great.
Can't wait to see you.
Eight weeks really is too long, Hal.
A lot's been happening around here.
A lot's happened to me too, Dad.
I mean, I feel like
I'm practically a new woman.
What's the matter? I cut myself shaving?
No, it's just... just seeing you
for the first time.
I mean, you know... in so long.
You look taller to me too, Dad.
Come on, squirt. Let's get home.
Oh, by the way,
thanks for all those newsy letters.
I'm really glad I bought you
all that personalized stationery
you just had to have.
- We meant to write, Dad, but we just...
- "We?"
Oh, me and my friend. I met this girl
at camp and we got really close.
Great.
Practically like sisters.
- She was a lovely girl.
- "Lovely girl?"
What, all of a sudden you're so proper?
- Still biting those nails, I see.
- Dad, you noticed!
What do you mean, "noticed?" You've
been biting them since you could chew.
But I've decided to stop, Dad.
It's a horrid habit.
"Lovely girl," "horrid habit."
What did I do, send you
to summer camp or finishing school?
And why do you keep saying "Dad"
at the end of every sentence?
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
I was doing it, Dad.
Sorry, Dad.
Do you want to know
why I keep saying "Dad?" The truth?
'Cause you missed
your old man so much, right?
Exactly.
It's because in my whole life - I mean,
you know, for the past eight weeks -
I was never able to say the word "Dad."
Never. Not once.
And if you ask me,
a dad is an irreplaceable person
in a girl's life.
Think about it. There's a whole day
devoted to celebrating fathers.
Just imagine someone's life
without a father.
Never buying a Father's Day card.
Never sitting on their father's lap.
Never being able to say, "Hi, Dad!"
or, "What's up, Dad?"
or, "Catch you later, Dad."
I mean, a baby's first words
are always "Dada," aren't they?
Let me see if I get this.
You missed being able to call me "Dad?"
Yeah. I really have, Dad.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Now you're starting
to sound like your old self.
Hello, gorgeous!
Oh, look at you!
Oh, you grew.
Oh, we missed you so much.
Hey. Don't you dare let your old man
talk you out of going back to camp, OK?
You're a growing girl. You need adventure.
- OK.
- You hungry?
I made corn bread and chili.
- Why are you so quiet? What's wrong?
- Nothing.
It's just I'm so happy to be home.
Hey, did I hear something
about corn bread and chili?
Yeah, it's on the stove. So...
Something's changed about you, Hal.
Hm. I can't put my finger on it,
but something about you
has definitely changed.
Really? Well, it's just the same old me.
Honest.
Hi, Sammy!
What is wrong with you, you goofball?
It's Hallie.
Oh, I probably just
smell like camp, that's all.
What's the matter with you?
It's like you didn't even recognize her.
Wow, it's even better than the pictures.
OK, kiddo.
What do you want to do first, huh?
You want to eat and then unpack,
or we could unpack and then eat.
Or we could eat while we unpack.
You mean I can eat in my room?
Yeah, it's a definite possibility.
Hey, Hal. When you're done, come on
down. There's someone I want you to meet.
- OK, Dad.
- OK, Hal.
Look at you, always eating.
- Did you tell her?
- No.
Oh, Nicky.
Tell me what?
Hal, it is none of my business how your
father makes a fool out of himself, OK?
- He's a big boy. He can do what he wants.
- OK, OK. So, who is she?
Her name's Meredith Blake.
She's a publicist from San Francisco.
Your father hired her
at the beginning of the summer
to do some publicity for the vineyard.
If you ask me, she's doing a better job
of selling herself than the grapes.
What do you mean?
Look, you and I both know your father's
not some kind of suave, debonair,
bachelor-of-the-month type.
So I gotta ask myself,
what does a hot young thing like that
see in a guy who walks around
with his shirttail hanging out
and a cereal bowl full of chili.
Then I realized there's about a million
reasons why that girl's giggling.
All of them are sitting
at the Napa Valley Community Bank.
You mean, you don't think
she even really likes him?
Ah, what do I know?
But I tell you one thing,
this one's got your father
eating out of the palm of her hand.
They do everything together.
They ride together, they swim together.
They go out to eat dinner every night.
Do you know what? Meet her. See
for yourself. Don't let me influence you.