- Taxi!
- Mr. Twistle.
- Yeah, hi.
- Hi. Chris Gardner.
Yeah, hi. Listen.
What can I do for you?
I submitted an application for the
intern programme about a month ago...
...and I would just love
to sit with you briefly...
Listen, I'm going
to Noe Valley, Chris.
- Take care of yourself.
- Mr. Twistle.
Actually, I'm on my way
to Noe Valley also.
How about we share a ride?
- All right, get in.
- All right.
So when I was in the Navy,
I worked for a doctor...
...who loved to play golf,
hours every day...
...and I would actually
perform medical procedures...
...when he'd leave me in the office.
So I'm used to being in a position
where I have to make decisions and...
Mr. Twistle, listen.
This is a very important...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This thing's impossible.
- I can do it.
- No, you can't. No one can.
- That's bullshit.
- No, I'm pretty sure I can do it.
- No, you can't.
- Let me see it.
Give it here.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wow,
you really messed it up.
Sorry.
It looks like it works around a swivel,
so the centre pieces never move.
So if it's yellow in the centre,
that's the yellow side.
If it's red in the centre,
that's the red side.
- Okay.
- So... You can slow down.
Listen, we can drive around all day.
I don't believe you can do this.
- Yeah, I can.
- No, you can't.
- Yes, I can.
I'm telling you, no one can.
See? That's all I ever do.
You almost have this side.
Holy cow.
- You almost had that one.
- I'm gonna get it.
Look at that.
You're almost there.
- 1710.
- This is me.
Good job.
- Goodbye.
- Yeah. I'll see you soon.
Where are you going, sir?
Excuse me, sir.
Where are you going, please?
Two... A couple of blocks.
- Just flip around.
- Okay.