You use Evyan skin cream.
And sometimes you wear L'Air du Temps,
but not today.
Did you do all these drawings, Doctor?
That is the Duomo,
seen from the Belvedere.
You know Florence?
All that detail just from memory, sir?
Memory, Agent Starling,
is what I have instead of a view.
Well,
perhaps you'd care to lend us your view
on this questionnaire, sir.
Oh, no, no, no.
You were doing fine.
You had been courteous
and receptive to courtesy.
You had established trust
with the embarrassing truth about Miggs.
And now this ham-handed segue
into your questionnaire.
It won't do.
I'm only asking you to look at this, Doctor.
Either you will or you won't.
Yeah.
Jack Crawford must be very busy indeed,
if he is recruiting help
from the student body.
Busy hunting that new one, Buffalo Bill.
What a naughty boy he is.
Do you know why he's called Buffalo Bill?
Please tell me. The newspapers won't say.
Well, it started as a bad joke
in Kansas City Homicide.
They said,
"This one likes to skin his humps."
Why do you think he removes their skins,
Agent Starling?
Enthrall me with your acumen.
It excites him.
Most serial killers keep
some sort of trophies from their victims.
I didn't.
No.
No, you ate yours.
You send that through now.
Oh, Agent Starling,
you think you can dissect me
with this blunt, little tool?
No.
I thought that your knowledge...
You're so ambitious, aren't you?
You know what you look like to me
with your good bag and your cheap shoes?
You look like a rube.
A well-scrubbed, hustling rube
with a little taste.
Good nutrition has given you
some length of bone,
but you're not more than one generation
from poor white trash,
are you, Agent Starling?
And that accent you've tried
so desperately to shed,
pure West Virginia.
What does your father do?
Is he a coal miner?
Does he stink of the lamp?
And, oh, how quickly the boys found you.
All those tedious, sticky fumblings
in the back seats of cars,
while you could only dream
of getting out, getting anywhere,
getting all the way to the FBI.
You see a lot, Doctor.
But are you strong enough to point
that high-powered perception at yourself?
What about it? Why don't you...
Why don't you look at yourself
and write down what you see?
Maybe you're afraid to.
A census-taker once tried to test me.
I ate his liver with some fava beans,
and a nice Chianti.
You fly back to school now, little Starling.
Fly, fly, fly.
I bit my wrist so I could die.